(The content of this drama is fictional.)
(Places, organizations, religions, and people are fictitious.)
What are you doing here?
We came here just in case you got beat up.
Let's not try to be cool and act alone.
Thank you anyway.
You should leave first. I'll take care of them.
You should follow them quickly.
Okay, I'll leave them to you.
I hate being in debt to people.
Is it all over?
Yes.
You completely beat him up.
Let's go to Ha Ri.
Why is he so full of energy?
He usually has a lot of energy stored.
Should we just leave him like this? Isn't he dead?
Should we just leave him like this?
Wait a minute. Please help me.
That person has a gun. He's on the wanted list.
- Wait a minute. - Stop, punk!
- Wait a minute. - Wait a minute.
- Let me go! - Gosh.
Stop!
- Hands in the air! - Hands in the air!
Hands in the air!
You punk!
Are you going to keep acting independently? Are you in puberty?
(The Last Episode)
Ha Ri.
Aren't you hurt?
What?
I'm okay.
Why would you play cheap and go solo like that?
Ha Ri... I mean, Su Hyuk.
Just call me as you did before. Su Hyuk, my foot.
All right. I know how you guys feel.
But I'll do this alone.
- Only I'm on the wanted list. - I'm on it as well.
He is too.
- What? - But not me.
Lucky you.
Why are you guys on the list? What happened?
When they were searching Prosecutor Jang's office,
I think they got their hands on ours as well.
He used to have data on us back when he was chasing us.
He doesn't know a thing about meticulousness.
All the more reason why you shouldn't get involved.
What do you mean? If we do this, we'll do it together.
He's right, and you don't even have a plan.
You don't know where "That Person" fled to.
Exactly. But we know.
What?
Don't tell me you guys...
- What do you mean? - Really?
Summon an emergency meeting this instant.
Gosh, why did they park their car here?
Many people pass by here. Goodness.
On my way up, I secretly attached it there.
Hey, this isn't all.
We also got Yoo Ki Hoon and Chairman Chun in custody.
Exactly. We pretty much ripped off their arms and legs.
And you still don't need us?
Unbelievable.
Everyone's on the wanted list except for Ah Ryung?
Fine, then. Let's do it.
All of us. Okay?
Byung Min and Jin Woong, get in my car.
Ah Ryung, get in the other car and follow us. Okay?
- We're taking two cars? - Yes, that'll be best.
Then I'll just go with her.
Just get in.
Okay, I'll go with Ha Ri.
I should go with him.
She drives too recklessly.
What do you mean? I'm the gentlest driver there is.
Right, come to think of it,
I was always carsick when I drove with her.
We'll go first, so follow us.
What is this?
Just follow us recklessly then.
Are you planning to do what I think you're going to do?
Yes.
That's the right thing to do.
I guess you're right.
What's your take on this?
I'm on the same boat.
Byung Min, the program still works on that car, right?
Oh, that? Yes, it does.
All right. Let's go.
Let's go.
Are you ready?
Yes, I am.
Are you sure you won't regret this?
This could be the end.
- I know, you punk. - Well,
it's no big deal to visit prison again.
I think I'm fine being incarcerated this time.
Last time, I was betrayed.
But this time, we're in this together, so it's okay.
So let's all hold hands and catch "That Person".
Do it.
All right. Let's see.
What?
Ha Ri, there's something wrong with the car, so let me check.
Ha Ri. Ha Ri.
Answer me!
Open the door.
Open it!
Ha Ri, open the door!
Open the door. Open it!
Thank you for everything.
Open the door!
Just open it!
Open it!
Ha Ri!
All right, we're almost there. Just a bit more.
I think it's that way.
- It's that one, right? - Yes, it is.
Look into it.
The control room is on the second basement.
There are two guards at each door at the lobby.
There are 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 patrolling guards.
And I'm sure there are many more on standby in case of an emergency.
Why are there so many guards in the middle of the night?
I know. Just like what you said, this may really be the end.
Let me ask you for the last time.
- Will you not... - We won't, okay?
I'm already extremely nervous.
Why are you acting like a talkative, old man?
Okay, let's go before we run out of time.
Go.
(Control Room)
Don't be ridiculous.
- Everything's fine, right? - Yes.
Are you done yet?
Gosh.
I found it! Hurry!
This is footage from 10 minutes ago. It's from the 25th floor.
Do you have any footage from the corridor?
There aren't any. That's really strange.
Strangely, there is everything except that.
Something is suspicious.
Look at this!
Aren't these punks from the Min Chang Party?
I saw them on TV.
We came just in time.
Cut the power and prepare the broadcast as planned.
You should also upload the data from the campaign.
I'll go to the meeting room and set up the cameras.
Ha Ri, you really have to come back soon.
It only takes three minutes for the power to come back.
- Okay? - Okay. Don't worry.
You really have to come back soon.
He's making me nervous.
- Gosh. - I can't believe this.
(Emergency Meeting)
Where is it?
Please sit down.
(Danger)
It's 3 minutes. 3 minutes.
You have to finish it within three minutes and leave no matter what.
Okay.
Three...
Two...
One.
What happened? Why did the power go out suddenly?
- Turn the flashlights on. - Okay.
We have to...
What's happening?
How are these punks managing the building?
I don't even have my phone.
Don't worry and just wait.
It will be restored.
Control room, do you copy?
Yes, we're restoring it. It will come back within 30 seconds.
Ha Ri, we don't even have 30 seconds left. Hurry, okay?
10 seconds left.
5, 4, 3,
- Did he do it? - 2.
Okay, we did it!
The positioning is perfect.
- Look at this. - Let's start the broadcast.
Let's call Prosecutor Jang before that.
- Really? - Okay.
If I do this,
you're going to pay for everything.
- Look at this. - What is this?
What is this?
Wait a minute.
That's right.
- It's them. - It is.
(Prosecutor, Jang In Gyu)
Prosecutor, look at this.
(Live, That Person Scandal)
Where is this coming from?
I don't know where it is, but it's a live broadcast.
Live?
That punk...
Prosecutor Jang, are you enjoying the broadcast?
You have to start working now.
Don't you know that you're wanted right now?
What if you get caught by doing this?
You're worrying about meaningless things again.
That's enough. Just clean up for us before it's too late.
You should take responsibility.
I heard that you were the one who proposed to Ha Ri to work together.
I'll leave the address by text message.
Hello? Wait a minute. You punk!
Punks. They shouldn't do this.
(Seon Building, Byeolsan-ro 3-gil 59, Jungeun-gu, Seoun City)
Let's prepare to move first.
- Okay. - Prosecutor, will you also go?
Yes.
I should take responsibility for my words.
Let's go.
Are we done now?
No. I don't think so.
We have to upload the data we got from the campaign.
- Yes. - Okay.
This will take care of everything.
Byung Min.
What is this punk doing here?
That crazy punk!
Darn it!
Is it you again?
10 seconds left.
- What? - Gosh.
Who are you?
What is happening?
What is he doing?
Is it you again?
We need to finish our talk.
Darn it!
You crazy punk, why did you go there?
Byung Min, let's just leave quickly.
That crazy punk loves being the center of attention.
Gosh.
It's Seon Building. You must catch those on the wanted list.
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
(PLAYER0404 has started streaming live.)
What are these fools doing?
Gosh, why isn't the door opening?
You're more resilient than I expected.
Thank you.
Who... who is this?
I thought this was a restricted area.
He is Prosecutor Choi Hyun Ki's son.
- What? - What did you say?
Choi... Choi...
The one from the Special Team?
That's correct.
You all know very well.
I'm the son of Choi Hyun Ki, the man you falsely accused...
15 years ago.
How could this be?
How does he know about the past?
Wasn't it supposed to be confidential?
It doesn't matter.
He will die in this room anyway.
- Hey. Hey. - Are you okay?
Hey.
- Hey, bring the emergency key. - Yes, sir.
(Emergency Meeting)
You haven't changed over the past 15 years.
Was Prosecutor Jang In Gyu the target this time?
To link him with the opposition party and the bribe?
Is that right?
Was Prosecutor Jang In Gyu the target this time?
To link him with the opposition party and the bribe?
- Please hurry. - Yes, sir.
Are you just going to listen to what he's saying?
What if he discloses all of this?
Don't worry.
The entire country will know about this by now.
What?
- What is he saying? - What?
- What? - Are we being filmed?
He is Prosecutor Choi Hyun Ki's son.
This is incredible.
I'm the son of Choi Hyun Ki, the man you falsely accused...
What is this?
15 years ago.
How could this be?
How does he know about the past?
Wasn't it supposed to be confidential?
It doesn't matter. He will die in this room anyway.
No...
We... We were being filmed.
What should we do?
- Sir. - You scumbag.
You said...
it only took a few lives and a scapegoat...
for you to control whatever goes on in this world.
You said that powerful individuals and conglomerates...
grovel before you in order to get something out of this world...
and that none of them would hesitate to do you such favors.
You're right.
You're not the one behind this. You're only a tool.
You're in that position thanks to those who are obsessed...
with power and money.
So I pondered.
"How can I play him?"
And I immediately got the answer.
You're a detestable voyeur who enjoys using and hiding...
behind foolish, old men in order to ridicule the people.
So it's only right for me...
to ridicule you in front of the people.
What will you do now?
No one will need you anymore...
because you'll be useless.
You son of a...
You completely ruined my plan!
I'll be off now.
You all have no business with me.
Don't be ridiculous, you scumbag.
Okay.
Do you think doing this...
will make me useless?
In your dreams.
This world is full of garbage like them.
These old men?
They can't do anything without me.
They are brainless fools...
who don't know what to do in order to get what they want.
Yes. I'm sure you're right.
But remember this.
If someone like you returns,
someone like me will definitely return, too.
[VIU Ver] OCN E14 The Player
"Justice is Served"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
You lost...
this game.
Hey.
Is it over?
You punks.
Yes.
It's all over.
You punk. Don't wander about wherever you please.
You look great smiling.
All right. We should also leave...
We should.
What did I expect? Gosh.
Hey, you! Stop right there!
Hey!
- My goodness. - Hello, sir.
You should leave the premises.
Let's run.
- Who are you? - What is this?
- Who are you? - What?
We're prosecutors from Seoun Provincial.
- What? - Prosecutors?
- What? - Wait.
Hello, I very much enjoyed the broadcast.
You're all quite famous now.
You went live in front of all the people.
It's a pity that I'm alive and well...
like this.
- You can take them. - Yes, sir.
- Wait. Hold on. - Come along.
- What are you doing? - Stop.
- Let me go! - Gosh.
- Jang In Gyu! - Let me go!
Don't you know who I am?
I'm not interested in who you were up until now.
- What? - What's important is,
you're no longer anything...
from this moment on.
You scumbag.
- Take him. - Yes, sir.
- Let's go. - You...
Let me go! Let go!
For the past 15 years,
I had been very curious.
I finally get to meet you.
You know what?
You look better on the screen.
You don't look that pretty in real life.
You're actually quite ugly.
- Please arrest him. - Yes, sir.
- Sir, we have a problem. - What?
What? They did?
Yes.
- Run! - Okay!
(Police)
Hurry.
Hurry!
Darn it!
I told them to stop following us.
Let's go.
Go get the key.
There's nothing's here.
What should we do?
There's nothing. What are we going to do?
Ha Ri. What should we do?
Gosh, we're going to get caught.
You idiot. What are you doing?
I told you not to follow me.
You're saying that again? Darn it!
I shouldn't have trusted and followed you. Gosh.
Hey, have you gone crazy? Are you smiling?
Gosh, is this funny?
My gosh.
Darn it!
The weather is darn good.
Hey.
We won't get to see each other for years.
For years, my foot.
You will rot in jail for decades for beating people.
Hey, I'll get out of prison before you, though.
Don't be ridiculous.
Hey, you passed the bar exam.
Whose crime is more serious? His or mine?
- You guys? - Yes.
How long are we going to be in jail?
Well... You both will be sentenced to life.
- Gosh. - You'll be sentenced to death.
He should be in a labor camp for life.
How can you be laughing at this moment?
- Gosh, I'm tired. - Is this funny?
I don't know.
Hey, wait.
We forgot to do something. I forgot it.
- What? - Give me your phone.
Oh, right. Darn it.
Hurry. Give me your phone.
(Police)
We're coming.
Open it now.
(Police)
We can't do it now.
- It's okay. Stop it. It's done. - I couldn't do it.
I need to do this.
What's that?
Hey, send it now. Hurry.
Get your hands up.
- All right. - Hands in the air.
I said, hands in the air.
- Get your hands up. - Okay.
All right.
Arrest them.
Gosh, go easy on me.
I'm afraid of guns.
Please go easy on me.
I didn't do anything wrong. I never hit anyone.
Gosh, I'm going.
Gosh.
(Police)
Wait. Stop right there. Wait.
Prosecutor Jang.
(Police)
- Prosecutor Jang. - Let go of me.
Well... These guys...
only cooperated with us on the investigation.
Let's go.
I guess he's a hawker.
Darn it. You selfish jerks.
All right. Come here.
Cha Ah Ryung.
You might get upset when you watch this.
But we just wanted to say goodbye.
I'll go first.
All right, Byung Min. You can go first.
Hello, Ah Ryung. It's me, Byung Min.
Is this right?
I used to teach you how to use a computer.
You should be careful of strangers.
You shouldn't use smartphone banking services at a cafe or something.
If someone hacks into the router,
they will steal all your personal information.
- Hey, it's my turn. - And the internet sites...
Let me go next.
- All right. Let's be quiet. - Gosh.
Ah Ryung. It's me, Jin Woong.
Ah Ryung, I don't need anything. Let me just say one thing.
Ah Ryung, the most important thing is your health.
If you keep eating instant noodles, I'll teach you a lesson.
- You should... - Stop eating instant noodles...
- and exercise more. - Hey, I'm not done yet.
- Hey, I'm talking. - You should work out.
Hey, go over there.
- All right. - This is important.
Cha Ah Ryung. Well...
We decided to live like this long ago.
But you didn't have a choice when you were younger.
So from now on,
you should live as you please and as you want...
with your own choices. Okay?
Listen to your heart.
I was happy that I met you.
And I had a lot of fun.
You have to be happy, okay?
- Be happy! - Bye.
- You should work out. - And one more thing.
Make sure to take the vitamins.
They always get their own way.
Even after the presidential election,
the video called, That Person Scandal is...
still going viral online.
The man in the video sent from an anonymous informant...
turns out to Yeon Je Seok.
And new evidence is found that he's been working as...
a political consultant of Min Chang Party for the past 15 years.
- My gosh. - 15 years?
He's also under suspicion that he has helped high ranking officials...
take advantage of loopholes in the law after committing corruption.
With the video and data...
provided by an anonymous informant,
the prosecution announced their plan to investigate the scandal...
as well as the presidential scandal from 15 years ago.
Meanwhile, it remains to be seen whether the late Mr. Choi Hyun Ki...
who was blamed for the scandal 15 years ago...
will have his name cleared.
Prosecutor Jang.
Do you really have to do this?
I just can't sneak out of this alone.
Still...
Investigator Kim Tae Hyun.
Investigator Hong Sung Min.
Investigator Jung Do Yeon.
Investigator Lee Hye Young.
Investigator Im Jin Dong.
Investigator Noh Young Il.
Thank you...
for all your hard work.
Please take good care of the rest.
Prosecutor Jang.
Sir.
(Witness Stand)
(Court)
(Defendant)
Witness.
Is everything you just testified the truth?
Yes.
It's all true, sir.
I requested that they help me with this case,
and it was me who ordered them to bring me the evidence.
Also, as for the illegal acts committed in the process,
using my discretion as a prosecutor,
I overlooked all of it.
That's ridiculous.
That man sure is a strange person.
Are you trying to take credit for all that we've done?
You'll overdo yourself by being so greedy.
We've never even met. Don't you think this is too much?
Please be quiet.
Witness.
Do you have evidence that can support your statement?
Yes, I do, sir.
This is the cell phone I gave them to use when communicating with me.
We normally communicated with this phone.
The call history...
has mostly been deleted because those guys hacked the phone.
But when I first asked them to do this job,
I made an audio file of our conversation.
The file's still left untouched on this phone.
You just have to bring me solid evidence.
It has to be hard evidence that'll catch them for sure.
As for any money you may happen to get in the process,
- we'll split in half. - Excuse me?
I'm just kidding.
You take it all.
- I can promise you that. - How can we trust you?
Everything we've discussed here today...
(5 minutes and 23 seconds)
has been recorded on this.
We'll communicate strictly with this phone.
(Defendant)
I'd like to submit...
this cell phone as evidence.
I approve.
Please play the recording.
I'll introduce myself to you formally.
I'm from the special investigation team Seoun Prosecutors' Office.
(Defendant)
(Judge's Bench)
Silence, please.
Witness. Are you trying to play jokes in court?
Your Honor, there must've been a mistake.
What are you doing? Turn that off this instant.
Yes, Your Honor.
Red flavor.
Don't look at me. I don't know.
I've reached my final judgment.
Inmate 3294, Choi Su Hyuk.
Including fraud, blackmail,
special larceny, robbery resulting in injury,
assault, and obstruction of business,
the defendant has committed a total of fourteen crimes.
Although the purpose of their actions was...
to punish criminals pursuing gain,
we cannot ignore the damage that was caused in the process...
or can we consider their crime as minor.
Therefore, I sentence...
the defendant Do Jin Woong to 12 years in prison,
the defendant Lim Byung Min to 12 years in prison...
and Choi Su Hyuk to 15 years in prison.
That's my final judgment.
One moment, please.
Wait a minute.
Let me have a word with him, please.
What's that look on your face?
Did someone die here?
Why did you do that?
You didn't have to do that.
Why are you guys taking the blame for what I did?
Who'll put those scumbags away if you go to jail?
- Don't you guys agree? - He's right, Prosecutor.
You should work harder for our sake, don't you think?
Forget about getting some rest in jail.
By the way, the money we earned doing this job...
has all been put away in a safe in our hangout.
You go collect it...
justly, that is.
What?
You're crazy.
Hang in there just a bit longer,
Jang In Gyu.
Prosecutor.
- Su Hyuk. - We'll be going now.
Prosecutor. There's a lot of money in the safe.
- Hide some of it for us. - Hurry up and go.
- Or maybe you can... - Hurry up and just go.
Forget what he just said.
I'll call you when I get out, Prosecutor.
(Ministry of Justice)
Su Hyuk.
Gosh.
I never imagined I'd ride in one of these vans.
It was in the "The A-Team" movie.
- It was, wasn't it? - Yes.
It's sure is snazzy though.
I still don't get it though.
Wasn't he too harsh sentencing 15 years just to me?
What did I do so wrong to deserve 15 years?
You're wrong. The judge made the right judgment.
You're the most vicious...
and on top of that, you were our boss.
If you think about, our country's judiciary sure is fair.
Indeed. Justice still prevails.
Justice?
If justice still existed, you two would get the death penalty.
Don't be ridiculous.
Darn it.
Just wait eight years. I'll go visit you two.
Did you say 8 years? You've been sentenced to 12 years.
As soon as I go in, I'll be a model prisoner.
You a model prisoner?
My goodness. That'll never happen.
What? You should watch what you say.
Troublemakers like you...
are the type that get beaten all the time.
You should worry about yourself.
Looking back, I think I had the most fun working with you guys.
I agree.
My life sure was full of ups and downs.
Oh, dear. I think I'm going to cry.
I suffer from narcolepsy. I'm narcoleptic.
- Get up, you jerk. - Hold on.
Manager. This is Chief Maeng you're talking to.
I'll keep a close eye on them. Don't worry. Take your time.
You're such a valuable person, so I've come to pick you up.
I can't seem to say no for some reason.
Hurry up.
You scum. Take this.
Why? Are you falling for me?
Stop right there!
You're amazing.
Watch out.
We made it.
Let's stay positive.
It was all there. Did you do it? Did you?
- Who did it? - Why did you do it?
- You shouldn't have! - Yes.
- All of us. - You punk!
- I should get my pay. Okay. - Me too.
Give me 30 dollars so that I can buy some chicken breasts.
- No. - He eats too much.
- Give it to me. - Don't use violence.
- Lower your chin. - Why should I?
1, 2... Okay!
1, 2...
Good job.
- Until when will you wear that? - Here.
That fool.
Say cheese.
- This will be uploaded. - Heart.
What is this?
- Nice! - Yes!
Good job, Ah Ryung.
This thing really goes!
- Gosh, Ah Ryung. - I like the shoulders.
They're just amazed by your beauty.
- Or we can pull a badger game. - A badger game? Who will?
I'm seriously going to kill you.
Who do you think? But seriously, who will?
- Cheers. - Cheers.
You're such a blabbermouth.
- You have a big mouth. - How could you?
I don't think that way of you.
Good work, guys!
Yes.
We had a blast.
Would Ah Ryung think the same?
Of course.
She will.
You know, I actually miss her.
At first, she was very rude, and I hated her guts.
I guess she grew on you.
How dare you brazenly mention my name after abandoning me?
Am I hearing things?
- Me too. - You too?
- You too? - Gosh.
Seeing how we're hearing things, I guess we really do miss her.
- Right? - Yes.
- Wait, what if it's a ghost? - Goodness.
- What if? - A ghost?
She can't be...
- dead, right? - Dead?
Why would I be?
What are you doing here?
- What is this? - Ah Ryung!
What's going on?
Prosecutor...
Jang In Gyu.
- What is this? - Ah Ryung?
Ah Ryung!
- What's going on? - Ah Ryung!
What was that?
- Look at him. - Hey!
You told me...
to live as I please from now on.
I chose to do this.
Prosecutor Jang, we found it!
You should've tipped us off.
You're really incredible.
I know.
Hey. Hold on, Ah Ryung.
What happened to our money?
(30 dollars)
This is everything.
Those punks.
- Are you okay, sir? - Yes.
Let's go.
I brought it with me.
- Really? - I knew it.
- Yes! - She really is a trickster.
She is.
Does this mean we're starting all over again?
All over again?
Strangely, I can't refuse this offer.
All right, then. Let's slowly start again.
- All of us, okay? - Let's do it!
- Okay! - Okay!
- Go, go, go! - Let's go!
Let's go!
- Yes! - The police are behind us.
We need to get rid of them!
Hey, step on the gas pedal!
- Let's go! - Okay!
- Nice! - Let's go!
(We thank our viewers for watching The Player.)
(The Player)
I have something
- To tell you - Look at them.
She pretty much shot a commercial.
- Why? - She really did.
Hello, viewers.
Hello, everyone.
That's good.
Good job.
Action.
Get out?
Come on.
Goodness, good job, everyone.
Good job and thank you, everyone.
Now, dance!